const level3Questions = [
  {
        question: "Ngân hàng",
        answers: ["银行 (yínháng)", "取 (qǔ)"],
        correct: "银行 (yínháng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tiền",
        answers: ["钱 (qián)", "七 (qī)"],
        correct: "钱 (qián)",
    },
    {
        question: "Chín",
        answers: ["六 (liù)", "九 (jiǔ)"],
        correct: "九 (jiǔ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tên riêng",
        answers: ["北京 (Běijīng)", "专名 (zhuānmíng)"],
        correct: "专名 (zhuānmíng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ngày, trời",
        answers: ["今天 (jīntiān)", "天 (tiān)"],
        correct: "天 (tiān)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ngày kia",
        answers: ["后天 (hòutiān)", "大后天 (dàhòutiān)"],
        correct: "大后天 (dàhòutiān)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tuần, thứ",
        answers: ["星期 (xīngqī)", "周末 (zhōumò)"],
        correct: "星期 (xīngqī)",
    },
    {
        question: "Thứ 6",
        answers: ["星期一 (xīngqī yī)", "星期五 (xīngqī wǔ)"],
        correct: "星期五 (xīngqī wǔ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Thứ 3",
        answers: ["星期二 (xīngqī èr)", "星期三 (xīngqī sān)"],
        correct: "星期二 (xīngqī èr)",
    },
    {
        question: "Thứ 7",
        answers: ["星期四 (xīngqī sì)", "星期六 (xīngqī liù)"],
        correct: "星期六 (xīngqī liù)",
    },
    {
        question: "Chủ nhật",
        answers: ["星期天 (xīngqī tiān)", "周末 (zhōumò)"],
        correct: "星期天 (xīngqī tiān)",
    },
    {
        question: "Cuối tuần",
        answers: ["周末 (zhōumò)", "星期日 (xīngqī rì)"],
        correct: "周末 (zhōumò)",
    },
    {
        question: "Hai",
        answers: ["几 (jǐ)", "二 (èr)"],
        correct: "二 (èr)",
    },
    {
        question: "Bốn",
        answers: ["三 (sān)", "四 (sì)"],
        correct: "四 (sì)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ở đâu",
        answers: ["哪儿 (nǎr)", "那儿 (nàr)"],
        correct: "哪儿 (nǎr)",
    },
    {
        question: "Biết, sẽ, có thể",
        answers: ["会 (huì)", "回 (huí)"],
        correct: "会 (huì)",
    },
];

export default level3Questions;
